紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   草草
翻譯   肉松
翻譯   鹽湖涼開水
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   蘇小黛
翻譯   國士章魚X
翻譯   軒轅喵
翻譯   Lynn_寧
時間軸   知之
時間軸   壬虛浪影
時間軸   萌
后期   餓得慌
顧問   老杜
校對   草草
總監   草草
紙牌屋
人人影視傾情奉獻
第五季  第四集
琥珀警報
僵尸出動了  去墓地看看
無信號
道·斯
全片完
派拉蒙電影
還有時間
康威拿下印第安納  密西西比  佛羅里達
諾克斯維爾投票中心發生事故
田納西州
諾克斯維爾
諾克斯維爾投票中心疏散
田納西州諾克斯維爾
湯姆·漢默施密特
《華盛頓先驅報》
取消           發送
康威拿下賓夕法尼亞
安德伍德總統是否已認輸
部分州不能認證結果
漢娜·康威就結果發表講話
艾·麥卡倫莉  我受不了了  對不起  麥卡...
大選之夜的混亂
這好像是個搖擺州派對
I smell a swing state party.
這和黨派關系無關
This isn't about party affiliation.
這事關國家安全
This is about security.
你要我們刻意壓制投票
You want us to engage in voter suppression.
我不會用那樣的字眼
It's not a phrase I'd ever use.
美國同胞們
My fellow Americans
哥倫比亞特區
the greater District of Columbia area
正在遭受疑似是哈里發國所為的網絡攻擊
have undergone what we suspect is an ICO-sponsored cyber-attack.
如果您的提議還有效
If the offer's still open,
我想接受增派警衛隊到俄亥俄州來
I'd like to accept additional troops for the state of Ohio.
現在在美國有四個穆罕默德·卡拉比
There are four Muhammed Kalabis in the United States.
其中兩個和哈里發國的卡拉比年齡相仿
Two are approximately the same age as the ICO Kalabi,
其中一個三周前進入美國境內
and one entered the United States three weeks ago.
我通常不會在這么晚的時候插進來
I don't get involved, not this late in the game,
除非我知道我能發揮影響
unless I know I can make a difference.
你眼睛都不眨一下地
You fucking lied, straight up,
對美國總統撒謊了
to the President of the United States.
安德伍德明天必輸無疑  他完蛋了
Underwood's gonna lose tomorrow. He's done.
這份九點的投票率是我們票倉的還是搖擺州的
This 9 a.m. turnout in our base precincts or swing?
票倉的
Base.
該死
Shit.
-有點低  -你說"低"是什么意思
- It's low. - What do you mean, "low"?
這是我們的地盤
This is our house.
我們絕不會離開
We are not leaving.
我不懂為什么數據這么低
I don't understand why the numbers are so low.
-根本沒道理  -投票率很低
- It doesn't make any sense. - Turnout's bad.
我聽說政治新聞網更重關注康威一方
I hear at Politico, they're concentrating mostly on Conway art.
閉嘴  不然就開除你
Shut up or you're fired.
...賽區對手
...division rivals.
這場斗毆很有看點
The fighting was quite a spectacle
但對冰球迷來說  不幸的是
but, unfortunately for hockey fans,
那是昨晚比賽中
that was just about the only action
唯一的看點
to be seen in last night's game.
威爾  馬克來了
Will, Mark's here.
希望你睡了會兒
Hope you got some sleep.
其實沒有
No, not really.
甚至跑了步  但...
Even went for a run, but...
你餓嗎
You hungry?
我只是想在今天
Um, I just wanted to connect
接下來的活動前  告訴你一下
before the rest of this day kicks in.
我跟馬歇爾談過了
I spoke to Marshall.
我告訴他了
No, I told him.
情勢很喜人
Things are looking good.
非常喜人
Very good.
我很想感謝你做的一切  那支廣告還有...
I really want to thank you for everything. I mean, the ad and--
那支廣告和我無關
I had nothing to do with that ad.
當然  但...
No, of course, but...
謝謝你的支持
to thank you for your support.
全靠你自己
This is all you.
聽著
Listen...
我...不想說錯話
I'm... choosing my words very carefully here.
你得準備好
You need to get ready.
今天會大獲全勝
Today's gonna be a good day.
你可以等進白宮再睡
You can sleep when you get to the White House.
但也未必
Or maybe not.
準備好吧  威爾  再見
Get yourself together, Will. I'll see you in a bit.
你準備好
Are you ready...
來"抓"我了嗎
to catch me?
道格  莉安  你們有空嗎
Doug, LeAnn... do you have a moment?
從山麓酒店現場發來的報道
Reporting live from the Piedmont Hotel,
現場氣氛很激烈
the excitement is definitely in the air right now.
最好別讓他們看到你證件上的名字
Better not let them see the name on your credentials.
那些人很愛戴他們的總統
Those folks out there love their president.
我很愛磅蛋糕
I love pound cake.
不代表它對我有益
Doesn't mean it's good for me.
你怎么樣  賽斯
How are you doing, Seth?
-你這里還有粉底沒抹勻  -天啊
- You got some foundation right here. - Oh, jeez.
我們還把這稱為新聞
And we call it the news.
我要做實況報道
I'm doing commentary.
那么遲早會有人問我
Which means eventually someone gets to ask me
我的文章有沒有影響到總統的敗選
if my articles affected the president's loss.
或勝選
Or his win.
祝你順順利利  賽斯
I wish you the best, Seth.
你還會找到工作的
You'll land somewhere.
你就是那種人
You're that type.
我們今晚會十分成功
We're going to have a great night tonight.
你沒必要哄我
You don't have to spin me.
我應該怎么說
How shall I say this?
我單身時  總是去敗選者的派對
When I was single, I always picked the loser's party.
我在鮑勃·多爾的宴會廳認識了
I met the last Mrs. Hammerschmidt drowning in tequila shots
正豪飲龍舌蘭的上任太太
at the Bob Dole ballroom.
而我現在...又單身了
And here I am... single again.
-你現在不在德州了  -道格  省省吧
- You're not in Texas anymore. - Doug, please.
-怎么了  -別以為你了解我
- Please what? - Don't think you know me.
我只是想確定你準備好...
Look, I just want to be sure that you're ready for--
麥卡倫會做他該做的事
Macallan will do what he has to.
我喜歡贏
I like to win.
獎杯  獎牌  焦灼的比賽  我都想贏
Trophies, medals, staring contests. You name it.
你能懂這一點  就能懂我
You understand that, you understand me.
大家好
Hello, everyone.
現在為時尚早
Well, it's still early.
今天的大選進程還遠遠沒結束
There's a lot more election to be had today.
我們只是想道個歉
And we just want to apologize that,
因為我們還有點工作要做
because we have a little more work to do,
我們沒法早點
we're not gonna be able to get over to the ballroom
抵達宴會廳了
as early as we would like to.
但等我們到了那里
But once we do get there,
我們就會跟你們每一位握手
we are going to shake the hand of each and every one of you,
感謝你們為我們所做的
to thank you for all the extraordinary work
出色工作
that you've done for us.
沒錯  為大家鼓掌吧
That's right, a round of applause all the way around.
我們等會兒派對上見
And we'll see you all at the party a little later.
好點了嗎
Better?
嗯  好了一點
Yeah, a little.
我第一次上了一位總統
First time I've fucked a president.
-不要這樣講  -馬歇爾說...
- Oh, don't say that. - Marshall said...
我還不是總統
I'm not a president yet.
就快了
Almost.
我得穿好衣服
I got to put on a suit.
-大家就要來了  -威爾
- People will be here soon. - Will...
你就不能允許自己感受一下嗎
can't you let yourself feel it?
就快了
Almost.
-您準備好就開始  先生  -請接通州長
- Ready when you are, sir. - Put the governor on, please.
-你好  -米切  我是總統
- Hello. - Mitch, this is the president.
我知道你聽過簡報了
I understand you've been briefed.
總統先生
Oh, Mr. President...
這讓我們猝不及防
this is catching us all off guard over here.
州的  當地的  我們都不知道
State, local, we had no idea.
我理解
I understand.
我跟副總統  和國務卿杜蘭特在一起
I'm with the vice president, the Secretary of State Durant,
反恐處助理局長格林也在線上
and on the line with us is Counterterrorism Director Green.
州長  很抱歉  但我們必須行動
Governor, sir, I'm sorry, but we needed to act.
我直接聯系了當地執法部門
I contacted local law enforcement directly.
我是過了好一會兒才知道
Well, it took a while to get to me.
米切  反恐處助理局長要與我們分享一些
Mitch, the Counterterrorism Director will be sharing information
絕不能外泄的信息
that we must keep amongst ourselves.
我們不想做任何會影響今天投票的事
We do not want to do anything that affects today's voting.
45分鐘之前
Forty-five minutes ago,
我們突襲了穆罕默德·卡拉比的住處  先生
we raided the home of Muhammed Kalabi, sir.
在戴德里克大街
On Deaderick Ave.
-嗯  -那里離體育場很近
- Yes. - It's near the Coliseum.
嫌疑人不在公寓里
The suspect was not in his apartment,
但是我們發現了制造炸彈的材料
but we did find bomb-making material.
-天哪  -米切
- Jesus, uh... - Now, Mitch...
我們最不希望的就是讓你恐慌
the last thing we want is for you to panic.
你一定要知道聯邦政府
You must know that you have the full support
會全力支持你
of the federal government here.
接下來怎么辦
Um, it... Well, what... what's next?
我們相信他的目標是某個投票中心
We believe his target is one of the voting centers.
我們知道你已經安排了警衛隊
We know you have soldiers in place,
采取了安全措施  設置了檢查站
security measures and checkpoints.
格林局長正趕去見你
Director Green is on his way to you.
聯調局諾克斯維爾辦事處會設立指揮中心
There will be a command center out of the FBI office in Knoxville
我們將進行協調
where we will coordinate.
我的家人今早就在體育場投了票
My family voted at the Coliseum this morning.
米切  聽我說
Mitch, listen to me.
不管你需要什么  我們都會提供
Whatever you need, we will provide.
俄亥俄的數字怎么樣
How are the Ohio numbers?
投票率這么低  不好估計
It's hard to gauge with turnout this low.
就是要這效果
That was kind of the point.
是對于另一方  不是民主黨
For the other side, not Democrats.
州長擔心了  你有什么數據嗎
The governor's worried. Do you have any numbers?
沒有  只有我們給過你的
No, just what we gave you.
我以為總統可能有
I would think that the president might have
我們接觸不到的數據
access to some numbers that we don't.
如果我有  你也會有
When I get them, you'll get them.
-我們很擔心  -堅持住
- We're worried. - Hang in there.
等過了3點這一波我再跟你聯系
I'll touch base with you after the three o'clock wave.
請讓我單獨待會兒  謝謝
If you could all just give me a moment, please. Thank you.
你最好去宴會廳
You better head over to the ballroom.
我們其中一人應該到場
One of us should make an appearance.
先生  這一天終于到了
Sir, the day has finally arrived.
是啊  讓我們看看這一天有多長吧
Yes, and let's see just how long this day lasts.
想像一下國安局給我打電話問
Imagine my surprise when the NSA called me
穆罕默德·卡拉比的事時我有多驚訝吧
about Muhammed Kalabi just...
你的電話隨后就到
moments before you did.
情況還在發展
Situation is still unfolding.
在選舉日
On Election Day?
弗蘭西斯
Francis...
跟你共事真是一段獨特的經歷
it's been quite a journey working with you.
卡拉比溜進了國內
Kalabi slipped into the country,
他正策劃著一起針對
and he's planning a terrorist attack
田納西某個投票中心的恐怖襲擊
against a voting center in Tennessee.
這種說法太嚇人了
And that is a terrifying proposition.
我需要你在白宮
Well, I may need you to stay around
再多待一陣  凱茜
the White House a bit longer, Cathy,
直到事態平息
until this situation is resolved.
好的
Of course.
我只是說
I was only saying...
這一路以來很不錯了
it's been a good run.
說得像她能激怒我似的
As if she could ever get under my skin.
我現在還不用去宴會
I don't need to get to the party just yet.
人們伸著汗涔涔的手想要最后一次向我致敬
Sweaty palms, eager to pay me their last respects.
但他們真正想用的致敬方式
When what they really want to do to show their respect
是把所有子彈都射向我
is to empty their bullets in my body,
確保我死得透透的
just to make sure that I'm dead.
帕特  抱歉讓你久等了
Patti, I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
哈維女士剛剛告訴我
Miss Harvey was just telling me
日程安排有變
that there's been a change in the schedule.
是啊  很不幸現在出現了緊急情況
Yes, unfortunately, we're in a bit of an emergency.
但我希望能盡快解決
But I hope it will be resolved soon.
湯姆  你好
Tom, hello.
-你認識耶茨先生吧  -認識
- You know Mr. Yates, don't you? - Yes,
黨代會上見過
we met at the convention.
莉安會在酒店
So LeAnn will be at the hotel.
要是你覺得
She can reach me
我應該早點而不是晚點過去的話  她會聯系我
if you feel I need to be there sooner rather than later.
萬一是晚點過去
In case it's later...
我希望你考慮一下四年后
I want you to think four years down the road.
-你說什么  -他們信賴你
- I'm sorry? - They trust you.
四年可轉瞬即逝
Four years is no time.
有輛車在等您
We have a car waiting.
我們今天還握手了
So we're shaking hands today?
我們還是保持那樣最好
I think it's best we keep it like that.
要握得像真格的一樣
Well, shake it like you mean it.
這樣如何
How's that?
你希望我直接去宴會廳嗎
So you want me to just head over to the ballroom?
不
No.
我確實喜歡穿過大房間看你
I do like looking at you across a large room.
勝利
Victory.
你贏的話用這份
This is for when you win.
敗選演說我也寫了一份
I wrote a concession speech as well.
全國上下的投票點都加強了安保
With increased security at polling places across the country,
今年進行投票的美國人
will fewer Americans vote for the president this year
會不會比以往都少
than in any election in recent memory?
尤其受關注的是典型的搖擺州
Particular attention is being paid to typical battleground states,
俄亥俄和賓夕法尼亞
Ohio and Pennsylvania,
在這些州  投票人數成了核心問題
where voter turnout has become a central issue
這可能決定本次歷史性大選的結果
that could make all the difference in this historic election.
費城的投票率如果很低
You know, if turnout is low in Philadelphia...
安德伍德夫婦就輸定了
the Underwoods are going under.
你得想個更好的開場白
You need a better in than that.
你看起像是被折騰得不輕
You look like you've been chewed up and shit out twice today.
似乎難以集中精力
Seems like you're having trouble focusing.
你看過醫生嗎
You ever see a doctor about that?
什么
What?
因為我自信可以診斷你是
Oh, 'cause I feel pretty comfortable diagnosing you
心事太重了
with too much on your fucking mind.
我請你喝一杯吧  我在慶祝
Let me get you something real. I'm celebrating.
兩杯奧本威士忌
Two Oban.
慶祝什么
Celebrating what?
你知道湯姆·漢默施密特的長期調查組吧
You know Tom Hammerschmidt's long lead team?
你面前的這位是新加入的成員
You're looking at the newest member.
那人真是永不放棄
That guy never gives up.
我告訴你他想干什么  你給他提供消息
I tell you what he's up to, feed him things from you.
現在談交換條件  有點晚了吧
Don't you think it's a little late for quid pro quo?
安德伍德夫婦仍有勝算
The Underwoods could still win.
等著瞧吧
We'll see.
無論如何  你都還有幾個月
Either way, you still have a couple more months.
也對
Yeah.
我會找到地方落腳的
I'll land somewhere.
你的電話
Your phone.
今天有人能讓我消停一會兒嗎
Can somebody give me a second today, you know?
該死  失陪一下
Shit. Excuse me.
你好
Hello?
有報告稱...
...while reports are coming in
諾克斯維爾一投票中心可能發生了襲擊
of a possible attack at a Knoxville voting center.
我們來看看直播...
Now, let's take a live look...
田納西州  田納西怎么了
Tennessee? What's going on in Tennessee?
目前場面非常混亂
...it's a very chaotic scene at the moment.
什么
What?
目前情況很復雜
...there's a lot happening right now.
當然  警方正在
Police are... are, of course,
試圖安撫民眾  并保證大家的安全
trying to keep everyone calm and safe here.
我們將為您帶來
And we will bring you...
你到底去哪了
Where the hell were you?
田納西  田納西到底怎么回事
Tennessee. What the hell's going on in Tennessee?
穆罕默德·卡拉比
Muhammed Kalabi,
敘利亞哈里發國的  燒肖像的那個
the ICO guy from Syria who burned the effigy.
有什么計劃
What's the plan?
今晚我站在你們面前  作為副總統候選人
I stand before you this evening as vice presidential candidate,
作為美國的第一夫人
as the First Lady of the United States,
最重要的  也作為這個偉大國家的一名公民
and most of all... as a citizen of this great country.
雖然諾克斯維爾投票中心發生了暴力事件
Despite the violent incident at the voting center in Knoxville,
此時此刻  總統正在進行處理
which the president is attending to as we speak,
我們想向任何在考慮不投票的各位保證
we want to assure anyone who's considering not voting
現在投票不僅是安全的  更是你們的責任
that it is not only safe to vote, it is your duty to do so.
不管你是民主黨人
It doesn't matter if you're a Democrat.
還是共和黨人
It doesn't matter if you're a Republican.
我們的國家需要你們今天去投票
Our nation needs you to vote today.
暴力不能導致冷漠
Violence cannot beget apathy.
我們必須發聲
We must make our voices heard.
賽斯
Seth!
有目擊者稱  諾克斯維爾投票中心
Witnesses report an FBI and Homeland presence
出現了聯調局和國安局的人
at the Knoxville voting center.
你覺得這事跟哈利發國有關嗎
Do you believe this is ICO-related?
賽斯  拜托
Seth, please! Come on.
-聯調局沒有回應  -你也別亂說  吉娜
- And the FBI isn't talking. - Neither are you, Gina.
這可不是發布會  我并沒做相關安排
This isn't a presser, because I didn't schedule one.
-我們只想知道  -兩次了  吉娜
- We're just trying to find out-- - That's two, Gina.
如果你想三振出局  我很樂意效勞
If you're looking for a strikeout, I'm happy to oblige.
不想嗎  很好
No? Good.
目前不接受提問
There's no questions at this time.
第一夫人的聲明里該說的都說了
The First Lady's statement stands as is.
我得到田納西的最新情況就會通報
I will have updates for you on Tennessee as I get them.
所有人都清楚了嗎  謝謝
Is everyone clear? Thank you.
賽斯
Seth!
我聽說一切都亂套了
I'm told everything just went wrong.
-聯調局派了拆彈部隊的人  -但是  米切
- The FBI had the bomb guys there... - But, Mitch...
天啊
...for crying out loud!
傷情僅僅是擦傷和瘀傷
...injuries didn't go beyond scrapes and bruises.
這我可不確定  肖娜
Oh, I don't know about that, Shawna.
有12人被送往了醫院
Twelve people were taken to the hospital.
格林的預計到達時間有了嗎
Look, is there any status on Green's ETA?
-斯圖爾特州務卿和我  -好的  請稍等
- Secretary Stewart and I... - Yes. Just a moment, sir.
-無法做出決斷  除非  -您得接這通電話
- ...cannot make a determination without-- - You need to take this.
什么  什么
What? What?
又怎么了
What the hell is this?
你好
Hello.
州長  我是馬克·厄舍
Governor. Mark Usher here.
我們應該在太陽谷的會議上見過
I think we met at the conference in Sun Valley.
對  沒錯
Yes, that's right.
真希望能在更好的情況下打來
Well, I wish I were calling under better circumstances.
我想知道您有什么需求
I wanted to know what you're going to need.
我可以盡快安排人過去  以防您...
I can get some excellent people down there fast in case you...
您似乎需要額外的安保  或者
you're feeling like you need the extra security or...
您還在聽嗎
You there?
在  我在
I'm right here, yeah.
幾分鐘前我跟肖娜談過了
I spoke to Shawna a few minutes ago,
我們一致認為絕不能讓選舉受影響
and we agreed that we absolutely cannot disrupt this election.
你聯系了我的州務卿
You called my secretary of state?
是她聯系了我
Well, she called me.
她是田納西州黨領袖  跟你一樣
She is a leader of the party in Tennessee. As are you.
需要我提醒你  先生  你那兒是共和黨州
Do I need to remind you, sir, that yours is a red state,
共和黨人都指望著你呢嗎
and every Republican in it is counting on you?
-謝謝  厄舍先生  -等一下
- Thank you, Mr. Usher. - Now, hold on.
肖娜只想問
Shawna just wanted to ask
能做什么  做不了什么
what can be done and what can't be done.
她跟我們其他人一樣  也在想辦法
She's like the rest of us, trying to figure this thing out.
因為目前尚無法確定的
Because of the scale of a possible threat
潛在威脅的規模
which we're still trying to determine,
也因為這些投票中心的重要性
and because of the importance of these, uh, voting centers,
我們請求州長宣布
we're asking the governor to declare
-進入緊急狀態  -威爾  你坐會兒吧
- a state of emergency... - Will, could you please sit?
這樣我們才能...
...so that we can provide more...
我不喜歡這樣
I don't like it.
3點那波說田納西無論如何都是我們的了
Three o'clock wave said Tennessee's locked up, no matter what.
...發生在這里的事件
...into the event that took place here...
親愛的  大家都看不到了
Love, no one can see.
怎么回事
What the hell?
可能會讓人不安
...be potentially disturbing.
有炸彈時狗不會叫的
They don't bark when there's a bomb.
什么意思"不會叫"
What do you mean, "They don't bark"?
有炸彈時狗不會叫  總統先生
The canine units don't bark when there's a bomb, Mr. President.
嗯  但整棟樓的人都聽到了
Yeah, but the whole building heard it.
他們的訓練是檢測到炸彈就坐下
They're trained to sit down when they detect a bomb.
-它們坐下了嗎  -沒有
- So did they sit down? - No.
那就是沒炸彈
Then there was no bomb.
我們認為狗叫是因為受到了刺激
We think the barking was provoked.
刺激  格林局長  這真是夠了
Provoked? Director Green, that'll be enough.
這些狗是我們最后的防線  先生
These dogs are our last line of defense, sir.
我覺得哈里發國今天闖進去了
I think ICO got in there today.
幸好他們沒引爆炸彈
And thank God they didn't get a bomb off,
但不管他們讓什么人混了進去
but whatever operative they got in there,
我覺得是去引發暴亂的
I think, was used to provoke the riot.
我說夠了
I said that is enough.
你覺得哈里發國會闖進樓里
You think ICO got all the way in that building
然后又決定還是不引爆炸彈了嗎
and then just decided not to set off a bomb?
-這個...  -我們不能影響投票
- Well, there are-- - We are not going to disrupt the voting.
米切  你好好勸勸他
Mitch, would you please talk some sense into him?
-我  -如果不暫停投票
- I-- - If we don't suspend,
局里無法確保中心的安全
the Bureau cannot guarantee the safety of these centers.
不可接受  找到卡拉比
Unacceptable. Find Kalabi.
州長不會希望
The governor does not wanna
在這么晚的時候頒發宵禁令
have to institute a curfew this late in the game.
-米切  -是  先生
- And, Mitch... - Uh, yes, sir.
你不能關閉投票
...you are not closing the polls.
你覺得我們該關嗎
You think we should?
我沒法發表意見
I can't weigh in on this.
我得跟肖娜談談
I need to talk to Shawna.
公眾還要承受多少丑聞
How many scandals should the public be expected to endure
才會說"夠了"
before they say, "Enough"?
會說"我不出門了"
Before they say, "I'm staying home"?
會對國家完全喪失信心
Before they lose complete faith in this democratic republic?
上次出現這樣的趨勢
This is a trend that dates back at least
是尼克松躲過牢獄之災的時候
to when Nixon avoided jail time.
好了  結束
Okay, we're out.
-真不錯  -我不需要粉絲  肖恩
- You're good. - I don't need fans, Sean.
只是真誠的欣賞
Just genuine appreciation.
喝一杯嗎  一杯是酒  一杯不是
Would you like a drink? One is brown and one is not.
-今晚會很漫長  -我聽說不是
- It's gonna be a long night. - That's not what I hear.
那么  田納西
So, Tennessee...
是問題所在
Is the question.
怎么樣
And?
我的男伴什么都不知道
My date knew nothing.
你在到處問了嗎
Are you making the rounds?
這里的人比我一般接觸的年齡要大
Crowd's a little older than I'm used to, but...
但是  沒錯  他們話多  卻沒什么料
yes, they're a talkative bunch... that don't say much.
我要酒
I'll take the brown one.
那是帕特里夏·惠特克  民主黨全國委員會主席
That's Patricia Whittaker over there. Chairperson of the DNC.
她有次在奧馬哈一家酒吧里扇了我個耳光
She slapped me once in a bar in Omaha.
我也不知道為什么
For the life of me, I can't tell you why.
田納西州有問題
There's something wrong with Tennessee.
你的男伴要么在撒謊  要么在抵賴
Your date is either lying or denying.
這是什么意思
What did you mean by this?
演講背后的字
On the back of the speech?
沒事  別提了
Nothing. Forget it.
"還有時間"
"There's still time"?
還有時間做什么
There's still time for what?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
你和你丈夫
You and your husband.
準備贏得選舉
Getting ready to win an election.
我看到你的樣子了
I see the way you're acting.
你知道我們今天打算贏得選舉嗎
Do you realize we have every intention of winning today?
當然
Sure.
但然后呢
But then what?
我以前會去緬因州的一間小木屋
I used to go to this cabin... up in Maine.
窗戶關不嚴實
The windows don't close properly.
整個夏天都能聞到大海的氣味兒
You can smell the ocean all summer long.
我覺得你還是去宴會廳吧
I do think it's better you go to the ballroom.
如果你尚未投票  我保證  你會有機會的
If you have not voted, I assure you, you will get the chance.
但出于良心
But I cannot, in good conscience,
我不能在確保安全前  允許投票繼續
allow balloting to continue until I am satisfied that it is safe.
為此  隨著夜晚將至
To that end, as nightfall approaches,
我要宣布今晚
I am announcing an enforced,
執行全州宵禁
state-wide curfew, effective tonight.
如果你中部時間晚8點30還未回家
If you are not in your home by 8:30 p.m. central time,
或是東部時間9點30
or by 9:30 in the eastern parts of this state,
你將被拘禁甚至逮捕
you will be subject to detention and possible arrest.
這是怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
我們會贏下賓州和俄亥俄州  就這么回事
What's going on is we're gonna win Pennsylvania and Ohio.
那么你就超過270了
That puts you over 270.
投票還在繼續  大家還在投票
The polls are still open. People are still voting.
我的直覺是那些票屬于我們
My gut says they're ours.
沒有田納西也272了
That's 272 without Tennessee.
那混蛋暫停了投票
That asshole's suspending the vote.
那得由他的州務卿決定  她是我們的人
That's up to his secretary of state, and she's on our side.
-都這樣了她還有的選嗎  -州長  聽我說
- She's gonna have a choice after this? - Governor, listen to me.
我們還要讓弗蘭西斯·安德伍德
I mean, how long do we let Francis Underwood
耍這種手段多久啊
get away with this kind of shit? Huh? How long?
他不會得逞的
He won't get away with it.
不會的
He won't.
剛剛是田納西州長
That was Tennessee governor...
相信我
Trust me.
宣布全州宵禁
...announcing a state-wide curfew.
扯淡
Bullshit.
全州的投票中心都在關閉
Voting centers all across the state are being shut down,
中部時間8點30或東部時間9點30前
and anyone not in their homes 8:30 central time,
還沒回家的人
or 9:30...
費城5點的一波  我們應該贏定了
Five o'clock wave from Philly. I think we're home.
...被拘禁甚至逮捕  這則公告...
...detention and possible arrest. This announcement...
田納西的事簡直瘋了
That Tennessee shit is crazy.
瘋狂事經常有
Crazy shit happens all the time.
這么湊巧
This convenient?
少來什么陰謀論了
Spare me the conspiracy talk.
政府沒那么大威力  或能力
The government's not that powerful... or competent.
總得問問
A man can ask.
目前安德伍德255  康威245
We're looking at 255 Underwood, 245 Conway.
賓州和俄亥俄呢
Pennsylvania and Ohio?
還是太接近  但就要6點了
Still too close, but it's almost six o' clock.
等我們把田納西州從康威變成搖擺
When we change Tennessee from Conway to undecided--
那么康威會下跌
That brings Conway down
-到...  -234  還是太接近
- to-- - Two thirty-four. Still way too close.
是啊  我們尚不知道
Yes, but we don't yet know
他已經拿下了西部州
that he's locked in the western states.
那些州十年沒變了
Those states have been locked up for ten years.
紅的  紅的  紅的  到今晚結束又會是紅的
Red, red, red and they'll be red again by the end of the night.
就看賓州和俄亥俄了
It's gonna come down to Pennsylvania and Ohio.
康威需要兩個州  你只需要一個
Conway needs both. You only need one.
馬修斯
Matthews?
他會反抗  可能還會公開表態
He'll push back. He might even go public.
另外五個州呢
What about the other five states in play?
律師在候著
The lawyers are waiting.
我們可以就壓制投票提出訴訟  但是
We can generate lawsuits, argue suppression, but...
還是不夠
Still not enough.
奧姆斯泰德在俄亥俄情況不樂觀  他很不高興
Olmstead's losing in Ohio, and he's not taking it well.
我今早跟他的幕僚長塔妮婭通過話
I spoke with his chief of staff, Tanya, this morning.
他在州北的情況很糟
He's getting clobbered in the northern part of the state.
克利夫蘭的低投票率也是個問題
Low turnout in Cleveland's not helping.
但他還能扭轉局勢
But he could still pull it out.
他贏不了的  他也清楚
He's not going to win and he knows it.
我們還有多少時間
How much time do we have?
俄亥俄州兩小時后關閉  大部分人今早都投票了
Ohio closes in two hours. And most people voted this morning.
有些州局勢已定了
Some of these states are baked in already.
克萊爾和我要單獨談談
Claire and I need the room for a moment.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
-莉安  我們再聯絡你  -是  先生
- LeAnn, we'll call you back. - Yes, sir.
你為什么讓他出去
Why did you ask him to leave?
因為我想再看著你的眼睛一次
Because I just wanted to look in your eyes one more time
再決定要不要動手
before we do this.
弗蘭西斯
Francis...
我們做吧
we're doing this.
他救不了我們  他發明了任期限制
He can't save us. He invented term limits.
道格
Doug!
再給我接莉安·哈維
Get me LeAnn Harvey back on the phone.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
對俄亥俄做該做的吧
Do what you have to do with Ohio.
我就去
I'm on it.
莉安  讓律師準備
LeAnn, get the lawyers ready.
-我不能這么做  -你可以的
- I can't do this. - Yes, you can.
-不不  -而且得馬上完成
- No, no, no, no, no! - And it needs to be done quickly.
太草率了
It's too sloppy.
是莉安打的電話  為什么是你來
Why are you here if LeAnn called me?
我還要向你解釋
Do I really have to explain to you
你不這么做的后果嗎
what will happen if you don't do this?
我不在乎他輸不輸
I don't care if he loses.
我不是指選舉  我是說你
I'm not talking about the election. I'm talking about you.
你會怎么樣
What will happen to you?
你有你需要的一切了  鏈接已經發給你了
You have everything you need. The Pastebin link was sent to you.
莉安呢
Where's LeAnn?
她不在  我時間不多了
She's not here, and I'm short on time.
州長  對不起  但這事只有一個辦法
Governor, I'm sorry, but there's only one way to play this.
我們需要你撤掉那三郡的
We need you to pull your poll workers
投票工作人員和投票機
and your machines from those three counties.
共和黨人會宰了我的  那是他們的地盤
The Republicans would crucify me. They own that area.
但那幾個選區
But those are the precincts
最有可能遭遇威脅
that are most likely to be threatened.
"可能"  你什么...
"Likely to be"? Hey, what are you...
這是什么意思
What are we talking about here?
恐怖襲擊可能性
Terrorist chatter.
針對田納西州的
Related to Tennessee?
是的
Yes, sir.
我可不能光聽你空口一詞
Well, I'm gonna need more than your word on that.
對不起  但情報是機密  州長
Oh, I'm sorry, but the intelligence is classified, Governor.
那給我權限
Then read me in.
我沒親眼
'Cause I'm not doing this
看到證據是不會這么做的
without seeing tangible proof with my own eyes.
你去告訴弗蘭西斯吧
You can tell Francis.
另外  因為俄亥俄州投票率這么低
The other thing is, with Ohio turnout so low,
可能會有人指控你刻意壓制投票
people could accuse you of engaging in voter suppression.
什么
What?
投票中心和警衛隊都是總統的主意
The voting centers and the troops were the president's idea.
但你同意了
But you signed on to them,
這才重要
and that's what matters.
你要輸掉選舉了  先生
You're losing your election, sir.
這很明顯
The signs are clear.
民主黨失去一位州長就太可惜了
That'd be a real shame for the Democrats to be down a governor.
但現在發生了種種情況
But here we have this confluence of events.
一方面是你不盡如人意的選情
Your disappointing returns on one hand
一方面是恐怖襲擊的可能
and the chatter on the other.
我需要證據  否則  人們會覺得
I need proof. Otherwise, people will think--
你為了贏得選舉  而關閉了
That you shut down voting in Republican precincts
共和黨選區的投票站
to guarantee your own win.
幸好
Now I'd say it's a good thing
國安局剛收到了可靠的消息
that the NSA just picked up on some credible chatter.
這危險的世界讓你別無選擇
This dangerous world left you no choice.
謝謝
Thank you.
州長  我剛剛拿到了機密情報
Governor, I was just handed the classified intel.
您在加密服務器上嗎
Are you on a secure server?
-在  -請稍等
- Yes, I am. - Please hold.
我這就把文件發給您
I'm sending the files over right now.
您的決定是正確的  先生
You're doing the right thing, sir.
我們可不能背上血債
We don't want blood on our hands.
我不管他們把投票機搬哪去
I don't care where they're taking the voting machines.
你就盯緊...
Just stay...
有必要的話把你自己綁在投票機上
You chain yourself to one of them if you have to.
好  我去找個俄亥俄州的法官
Good. I'm gonna find an Ohio judge.
俄亥俄州的投票中心已經關了近兩個小時了
Voting centers in Ohio have been closed for almost two hours.
康威已經去找法官了
And Conway's got a judge.
他在申請重開投票中心
He's petitioning to reopen.
但就算投票中心繼續關閉
But even if they stay closed,
俄亥俄州能幫我們達成目的嗎
would Ohio get us there?
其他州可能還有戲
Other states might be in play.
壓制投票的傳言也出現了  但...
Rumblings of suppression are out there, although...
還有什么別的情況
Well, what else do we have?
愛達荷州  出現恐嚇選民的事件
Voter intimidation in Idaho.
怎么樣  我要不要回話讓他們提交訴訟
What do you think? Should I call them back and have them file?
我看行
I like it.
這樣和田納西的事呼應效果最好
It has the most resonance with what's happened in Tennessee.
我還希望佐治亞有議員站出來
I also like an assemblyman we have in Georgia.
馬里蘭有個眾議員
There's a congressman in Maryland.
馬里蘭也是沒要求派警衛隊的州之一
That's one of the states that didn't request the troops.
等等  我們需不需要普通選民出來表態
But wait. Don't we need something coming from a voter?
密西西比有個選民
There's a voter in Mississippi.
她說她嚇得不敢去投票了
Said she was too scared to vote.
新聞基本就是告訴她不要去投票
That TV essentially told her not to go.
這就有點牽強了吧
Well, that sounds like a bit of a stretch.
可能對我們有利  先生
That could be a plus for us, sir.
能很好地打開局面
Really open things up.
如果俄亥俄繼續關閉
If Ohio stays shut,
可能會引發連鎖反應
there could be a ripple effect.
這都是前無古人的做法
This is all uncharted territory.
那好  佐治亞和馬里蘭待會兒再說
All right, let's put a pin in Georgia and Maryland,
讓俄亥俄的投票中心繼續關閉
and let's keep the Ohio voting centers shut down,
看看有什么結果
and see where that gets us.
康威已經拿下賓夕法尼亞
Pennsylvania has gone to Conway.
就算雙方在俄亥俄仍然難分勝負
Even if Ohio is still too close to call
總統在西北部取勝的話
and the President does well in the Northwest,
他仍無法抵消康威在南部取得的優勢
he can't counter Conway's gains in the South,
而那里曾是安德伍德的地盤
in what would typically be Underwood territory.
人民已經做出了選擇
The people have spoken.
真是難以置信
I can't believe this.
總統因故不能前來  他向各位表示歉意
The President apologizes that he couldn't be here tonight,
但他想讓我告訴各位  敗選已經不可避免了
but he wanted me to let you know that concession is inevitable.
還有那么多州票沒計完
All the states haven't been called yet.
總統還有時間想辦法...
The president still has time if he needs...
各位  我們已經盡力了
Guys, we fought a good fight.
可是很不幸  實情就是這樣
But, unfortunately, this is the reality of the situation.
天啊
Jesus.
看來這就算完了
Well, I guess that's that.
喂  我是威爾
Yeah, this is Will.
我想第一個對你說
I wanted to be the first to tell you
恭喜你  當選總統先生
congratulations, Mr. President-elect.
謝謝你  總統先生
Well, thank you, Mr. President.
2000年大選夜  戈爾先向小布什認輸
但是第二天又反悔了
怎么  你以為我沒從戈爾那里學到教訓嗎
What? You think I learned nothing from Al Gore?
我們這場選戰可真是激烈萬分啊  是不是
We kept them on the edge of their seats, didn't we?
我想這也說明我們的體制運轉良好
I guess that means the system is working.
我也這么看
I guess it does.
你是我遇到過的最強勁的對手了  弗蘭西斯
You're about as tough an opponent as they come, Francis.
我經驗豐富啊
Well, I've had a lot of practice.
請一定要轉達我對漢娜和孩子們的問候
Now, you be sure to give my regards to Hannah and the children.
謝謝你  總統先生  我
Thank you, Mr. President. I'm...
我在不久的將來  肯定會向你討教的
sure I'll be calling on you for advice in the very near future.
我萬分期待
Well, I look forward to that.
他認輸了
He conceded?
對
Yeah.
我們成功了
We did it.
我們做到了
打擾一下  先生
Excuse me, sir.
布洛哈特將軍正在來套房的路上
General Brockhart is on his way over to the suite.
謝謝
Thank you.
有消息源稱  不久前
Sources are telling us that Francis Underwood
弗蘭西斯·安德伍德致電康威州長
conceded to Governor Conway on the phone
承認落選
only a short time ago.
我猜測他們收到的數字跟我們的相符
I suspect their numbers are matching up with ours,
那么俄亥俄將被共和黨收入囊中
which would put Ohio in the Republican column.
足以讓威廉·康威
Enough to make William Conway
成為美國下一任總統
the next president of the United States.
-你好  -塔妮婭  讓他接電話
- Hello? - Tanya, put him on the line.
等一下  我看看能不能找到他
Hang on, let me see if I can get him.
他是我的州務卿
He's my Secretary of State,
他有權這么做
and he has the power to do it.
那你得告訴他該做什么
Well, then you need to tell him what to do.
他說他可以重開選站將投票日延長到明天
He says he can reopen and extend the voting day into tomorrow.
告訴他這不安全
Tell him it's not safe.
我說了  道格
I've done that, Doug!
他顯然不在乎
Obviously, he doesn't seem to care.
安德伍德已經認輸了
Underwood conceded already.
別放你的州務卿出去
Do not trot out your Secretary of State.
投票不能重啟
Voting cannot resume.
如果你還有什么疑慮
Now, if you have any doubt,
那也給我忍著
you swallow it right now.
我擔心的是黨派
I'm worried about the party.
這對黨派的影響
What this could do to the party.
羅杰  這比黨派重要多了
Roger, this is so much bigger than the party.
我覺得我把我的事業都賭上了
I feel like I'm risking my entire career here.
是的
You are.
如果你不照我說的做
And if you don't do what I'm telling you,
你的前途就完了
it's over for sure.
怎么了
What?
他還要耗多久
How many hours is it gonna take him
才肯在公眾面前說出那幾個字
to spit out the fucking words in public?
不管了  去他的規程
Screw this. Screw protocol.
我這就要過去
I'm heading down there.
-不  不行  -已經到第二天了  馬克
- No, you're not. - It's already tomorrow, Mark.
這簡直不可理喻
I mean, this is insane.
-我想發表講話  -俄亥俄州還沒完
- I want to make my speech! - Ohio is still in play.
什么
What?
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
持續的恐怖主義威脅帶來的恐慌...
...fear from continued terrorist threats
和田納西州傳出的令人不安的消息
and the disturbing news coming out of Tennessee...
讓我不得不關閉幾個我們的投票站
I was forced to close a number of our polling places.
操
Fuck me.
經與俄亥俄州州務卿達成一致
And in accordance with the Ohio secretary of state,
投票在進一步通知前先行暫停
the vote is suspended until further notice.
我知道這會讓我們的選民疑慮重重
Now, I know this may put our electorates in question...
但我別無選擇
...but I had no choice.
新澤西可能不認證
New Jersey might not certify.
出現了一些異常情況
There's been a variety of irregularities.
伊利諾伊也是
Same with Illinois.
看起來內華達也有異動
Looks like Nevada's making noises, too.
感覺似曾相識  你有同感嗎
I'm having déjà vu. You ever get that?
你真的在問我似曾相識的感覺嗎
Are you seriously asking me about déjà vu?
算了  已經沒感覺了
Never mind. It's gone.
你從未有過似曾相識的感覺嗎  人人都會有
You never get déjà vu? Everybody does.
我沒有
I don't.
別那么焦慮  道格
Don't look so worried, Doug.
你就是那一瞬間感覺很熟悉
You just felt familiar for a second.
已經過去了
It's over.
現在  總統選舉結果未定
Now, the presidency hangs in the balance.
至少六個州將不能在2016的選舉夜
At least six states will not have certified vote totals
認證計票結果
on Election Night 2016.
晚上好
Good evening.
我猜我該說早上好
I guess I should say good morning.
威爾很希望他能親自出鏡
Will wishes he could be here himself...
但我們獲知那有違規章
but we've been advised that goes against protocol.
我知道...
I know...
你們很失望
you're disappointed.
你介意用失望這個詞嗎
Are you okay with the word disappointed?
我們不該提到他們的憤怒嗎
Shouldn't we acknowledge their outrage?
我覺得我們應該小心處理
I'd say we should tread lightly.
目前我們只想請他們保持耐心
For now, we're just asking for their patience.
好  我們拍吧
Okay, let's do it.
這個國家就沒有無聊的時候
Never a dull moment in this country.
威爾很希望他能親自出鏡
Will wishes he could be here himself,
但我們獲知那有違規章
but we've been advised that would go against protocol.
我知道你們很失望
I know you're disappointed
你們所期待的改變
that the change you were hoping for...
你們所投票支持的改變
...that you voted for,
得再等一段時間
has to wait a little longer.
最終  這沒有定論的選舉之夜
And, finally, a night of electoral indecision,
幾乎每個州都提起了訴訟
with lawsuits being filed in nearly every state,
為它畫上句號的是檀香山市長
has ended with the mayor of Honolulu,
最后一個關閉了投票
in the last state to close its polls,
并拒絕承認選舉結果
refusing to honor the results of the election
還提起了訴訟
and filing a lawsuit.
夏威夷是我們這邊的嗎
Was Hawaii one of ours?
應該不是
No, I don't think so.
克萊爾  能幫我個忙嗎
Claire, could you do me a little favor?
我頭很痛
I have a splitting headache.
你能揉揉我的太陽穴嗎
Could you rub my temples for a moment?
當然
Of course.
不  其實是我眼睛這里疼
No, actually the pain is right behind my eyes.
你能...給我揉揉眼睛嗎
Could you just... rub my eyes for me?
但是你討厭那樣
But you hate that.
我知道  但是這次我應該會喜歡
I know, but I think I'll like it this time.
你可以用力點
You can do it harder.
再用力點
Even harder than that.
走出這一步就沒有回頭路了
There's no coming back from this.
我很清楚我們要做什么
I know exactly what we're about to do.
如果我們失敗了  后果要我們兩個承擔
If we fail, it's on both of us.
我是不能保護你的
I won't be able to protect you.
那就如釋重負了
And what a relief that will be...
對我們兩個都是
for both of us.
美國人民不知道什么對他們才是最好的
The American people don't know what's best for them.
我知道
I do.
我很清楚他們需要什么
I know exactly what they need.
他們就像小孩子  克萊爾
They're like little children, Claire.
我們從未有過的孩子
Children we never had.
我們得抓著他們黏糊糊的手指
We have to hold their sticky fingers
擦干凈他們的臟嘴
and wipe their filthy mouths.
教他們分辨是非
Teach them right from wrong.
告訴他們思考什么
Tell them what to think
感覺什么  想要什么
and how to feel and what to want.
他們甚至連書寫最瘋狂的夢想
They even need help writing their wildest dreams,
塑造最大的恐懼都需要幫助
crafting their worst fears.
他們很幸運
Lucky for them...
他們有我...
they have me...
他們有你
they have you.
安德伍德
Underwood.
2016年
2016.
2020年
2020.
2024年
2024.
2028年
2028.
2032年
2032.
2036年
2036.
一個國家
One nation...
由安德伍德執掌
Underwood.
道格  莉安  你們有空嗎
Doug, LeAnn... do you have a moment?
按約定俗成的規則  正常的選舉程序  是在選舉結果揭曉后
落敗方向勝選方打電話認輸  然后發表落選演說  再由勝選方宣布勝利
競選雙方在這件事上  按說要本著"大局為重"的原則
就是不能讓勝負的結果影響選民對民主制度的信任
所以如果選舉中出現選票極其接近的情況  而落后方要求重新計票
落后方會面臨壓力  不能讓這個懸而未決的時間拖得太久  造成混亂
但如果有候選人想糾纏下去  拖上幾個月  也并不被法律禁止
在2016年大選夜  希拉里開始并不甘心認輸
是奧巴馬親自給她打電話  要求她認輸  她才給特朗普打電話承認落選
但她并沒去自己的選舉中心會場公開認輸  并感謝支持者
而是在午夜后派自己的競選經理去會場  告知支持者事情還沒完
媒體是在她不會親臨現場后  才得知她致電特朗普認輸了  當時場面混亂
美國建國時并沒有任期限制  但是首任總統華盛頓高風亮節
擔任兩屆總統后就堅決退休  所以后來者也就約定俗成地只任兩屆
格羅弗·克利夫蘭是美國唯一一個卸任后重選再度當選的總統
他是第22任和第24任總統  都只任了一屆
但到了富蘭克林·羅斯福的時候  因為他影響很大  又遇上二戰
所以當他兩屆任期結束后決定繼續做總統時  并沒有遇到太多阻力
他的支持者稱  他繼續擔任總統是為了戰爭需要
羅斯福四次勝選  但是最后一次被選上后不久就因病去世
他的行為被認為是對民主制度的威脅
于是國會在1944年通過了憲法第22條修正案  規定總統最多只能任兩屆
在副總統中途繼位的情況下  也最多只能擔任10年